Guide to the Jane LaTour Papers WAG.317
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Vocational Education, 2005, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 7, Box 36, Folder 18)
- Women and the Civil Rights Movement, 2002-2009 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Women's Conference Address List, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Women and the Glass Ceiling, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Women at Ground Zero, 2001-2008 (Box 32, Folder 11, Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 9)
- Women on the Job, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Women in Non-Traditional Jobs, 2005-2009 (Box 30, Folder 7, Box 31, Folder 1-3)
- Women's Rights, 2007-2010 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Women's Suffrage, Feminism, and Abortions, 1998-2003 (Box 32, Folder 14, Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 10)
- Women and the Supreme Court, 2006, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- "Women in Trade" - Jane LaTour's Research Bibliography, 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Working Mothers, 2003-2007 (Box 33, Folder 2, Box 36, Folder 19)
- Working Theater Open Mic, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 3)